[{"answer": "It's not that simple because they have to come up, Piers, with some sort of compromise, they have to come up with come sort of plan that can pass the Senate and but then go back to the House of Representatives and pass there -- something that the president could sign that would allow the United States to raise the debt ceiling and avert some sort of financial disaster come Tuesday.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 8, "question": "Is it as simple as, sorry, you are Republicans, we didn't like the bill -- we're Democrats, we're not having it?", "qSentId": 7}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "Jessica, it's been a day of frantic arm twisting, but we've ended up really absolutely nowhere, haven't we?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'm sure you recall the speech that was given to the American people on Monday night by Speaker Boehner.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Senator Durbin?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Oh, I think Senator Schumer laid that out pretty clearly.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "What is your contingency plan if this doesn't get through the Senate?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "It's up to the Republicans.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "I know you're calling for Leader McConnell to come to the table and negotiate, but what is the way forward from here?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "CBO has come up with those numbers and I told you before, we have laid out all the numbers, you can dissect them, look at them.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Are all of the increased savings due to (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "And I heard a report earlier and maybe you can confirm this, that Speaker Boehner and the president haven't actually exchanged a single word in five days?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Well, it's nice no chat with you, Piers.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "I mean, you are so way out of step with public opinion, aren't you?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "No, I think what they think is unreasonable, is not a question of being partisan.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "It doesn't even get debated, don't you think, Piers, that's a little unreasonable?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Well, what you do is you look at House Republicans, twice, not once, but twice.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "How exactly do you guys expect this country's economy to recover?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Well, there's clearly, Piers, an internal battle going on within the Republican Party right now.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Where are we with this?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Where is that compromise?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "No, I don't think Speaker Boehner has lost any of his power.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "What's been happening?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "I'll tell you this, Piers.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Who is taking responsibility for this?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Well, it's kind of interesting that you say 64 percent are willing to raise taxes when we know that 47 percent of wage earning households in America don't even pay taxes.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not looking for anyone to resign.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Finally, Allen West, should we go to default here, an unprecedented catastrophe in the history of America, who has to resign?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "I think it will be a blow to both, probably roughly equal, depending on how you look at it.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "But would it be a massive blow to the Democrats or more of a blow to Republicans?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "If I could have my way, cut, cap and balance would be law of the land.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "How would do you that?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Look, we're a democracy.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Are you aware of the rising sentiment around the world that this is looking fairly shameful for the American political process?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Well, I actually think there are three things going on that make for high drama and a lot of frustration, as you have been describing on your program.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Well, I think there are many Republicans who oppose balanced budget.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "He has a point, doesn't he?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Business booming, right?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Well, you know, we're a pizza company.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "What do you think the answer is?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "You're a bipartisan operation, are you?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "Last night was a relatively good-sized order, 20 pizzas up to Representative Boehner.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "How many pizzas did you actually deliver last night?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "You know, that's a good question.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Is he on the spicy side of life?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "I believe it was credit.", "docId": "110729pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "And did they pay cash or credit?", "qSentId": 586}]